Another important thing to do for your dog is always have one spot in the house that's devoted for the dog for sleeping, resting, relaxing, whatever.
In this case, we have an extra bedroom and I let Possum sleep on the bed in here.
She doesn't get on the other bed unless I call her up there.
A lot of people don't like dog hair on the bed or whatever.
It doesn't bother me.
I just tend to wash my sheets more.
In this case, I let Possum have her very own bed.
She knows that she doesn't have to get on any other piece of furniture, that she always has this to come home to.
Now, if we have guests over, then what I do is I make a little pillow in the corner and she can sleep on that and she knows that that's her bed because it has her blanket that she has.
I always bring her in here to my office so I can work and have her near me, and she's like my shadow.
She stays really close all the time and has ever since she was a puppy.
Not everybody can devote that kind of time, but you can devote enough love to give your dog its own little bed so it can always have somewhere to rest and sleep, and they love you back for that.
Don't you Ms. Possum?
See she's asleep.
She's sleeping like a baby.